rackaid.com 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy - Server Support & Management by rackAID

This privacy statement covers the site www.rackaid.com and associated services.

 **Definitions and Scope**  
Herein the term “users” refers to all visitors to our web site while the term “clients” refers only to individuals or businesses whom have purchased rackAID® LLC’s products or services.

This agreement largely focuses on the general use of the rackAID® LLC site. If you use rackAID® LLC’s services, the terms and conditions discussed herein are superseded by the policies outlined in our service agreement. Clients concerned about the privacy of their information should see our service agreement.

 **Disputes**  
If users or clients have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact rackAID® LLC by email or by the online feedback form. If users or clients do not receive acknowledgment of their inquiry or their inquiry is not satisfactorily addressed, they should then contact the Better Business Bureau (BBB). The BBB will serve as a liaison with the rackAID® LLC to resolve users concerns.

 **Information Collection**  
rackAID® LLC is the sole owner of the information collected on www.rackaid.com. rackAID® LLC collects information from our users at several different points on our website as part of our standard operating procedures.

 **Registration**  
In order to use certain parts of this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which the user has expressed interest. rackAID® LLC may require the user to provide demographic information, and unique identifiers (such as, username and password) to access restricted areas of www.rackaid.com or to deliver requested services.

 **Service Requests**  
We request information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and mailing address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date) as well as information relevant to completing the requested services. This information is used to fulfill the service request. If we have trouble processing a service request, the information is used to contact the user. In addition to this statement, all service work is covered by the terms and conditions established in our service agreement. Clients should review our service agreement for complete details relating to our non-disclosure policy and security measures.

 **Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once the user closes the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

Cookies are used on our site for tracking web page statistics. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

 **Third Party Advertising**  
Where advertisements appear, they are delivered to users by Google. Information about the user’s visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not user name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.rackaid.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. Please consult the respective partners’ and advertisers’ for details on their privacy policies.

 **Log Files**  
Like most websites, we collect log files indicating the time, method, and pages accessed on our site. Log files include Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and cookie information. This data is used to provide demographic information for aggregate use of the site. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use a tracking utility called Urchin that uses the log files to analyze users’ interactions with the site.

 **Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)**  
We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by providing detailed tracking information. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. The main difference between the two is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear gifs are not tied to users’ personally identifiable information.

In addition, we use clear gifs in our HTML-based email marketing campaigns to let us know which emails the recipients have opened. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If users would like to opt-out of these emails, please see the Opt-out section.  
Communications from the Site

 **Special Offers and Updates**  
Users that subscribe to our newsletters forums or other subscription-based services may receive a welcoming email to verify services and contact information. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections. Clients should refer to our service agreement for more information about communications from rackAID® LLC.

 **Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users’ privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.

 **Service Announcements**

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send users an email to notify them of this outage. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications; however, these communications are not promotional in nature.

 **Customer Service**  
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account. We may reply via email, phone or in writing in accordance with the user’s wishes. If the user is also a client, the terms and conditions set forth and our service policy will dictate our communication methods.  
Sharing Information

 **Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

 **Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**  
We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

 **Third Party Intermediaries**  
Sometimes rackAID® LLC may be required to communicate directly to a third party an effort to provide our users with a better quality web site. In these cases, we will obtain your permission to disseminate your information to the third party. For example, we may need to communicate directly with your ISP to determine why your newsletter is not being delivered.

 **Business Transitions**  
In the event that rackAID® LLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.  
Choice/Opt-out

 **Opting Out**  
Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. For example, our order form has an ‘opt-out’ mechanism so users who buy services from us, but do not want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at unsubscribe@rackaid.com. We also offer an opt-out mechanism on the web site or the user may contact us by mail to opt-out.

 **Outside Parties**  
Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party.  
Special Considerations

 **Links**  
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, rackAID® LLC, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites even if those sites are owned and operated by rackAID® LLC or its affiliates. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site, www.rackaid.com.

 **Surveys & Contests**  
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and mailing address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. If a contest includes public disclosure of the winner, the sign up form will indicate this requirement.

Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site and our services. Users’ personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice to the user. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, they may not use users’ personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes nor retain the information longer than the time we specify.

 **Tell-A-Friend**  
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. rackAID® LLC will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. rackAID® LLC stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and preventing fraudulent use of the referral service. The friend may contact rackAID® LLC at remove@rackaid.com to request the removal of this information from our database.

 **Chat Rooms, Message Boards, and Public Forums**  
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online – for example on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas – that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return that are unrelated to rackAID® LLC or this web site.  
Security

 **Website Security**  
This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, their information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry – SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just ‘surfing’. We use GeoTrust 128 bit SSL certificates for this site.

 **Offline Data**  
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users’ information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a monitored, secure physical environment.

 **Supplementation of Information**  
In order for this Web site to properly fulfill its obligation to users it may be necessary for us to supplement the information users provide with information we receive from third party sources. We may purchase third party marketing data and add it to our existing user database to better target our advertising and provide pertinent offers we think our users would be interested.

 **Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires the use of our web site, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ personally identifiable information. This can usually be done at the removal request form or by emailing our Customer Support at remove (at) rackaid.com. Or, contact us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. Please note that if you have conducted business with rackAID® LLC, we will deactivate your account but retain all information relating to your account in accordance with the terms specified in our service agreement.  
**Third Party/Public Disclosure**

If a client or an agent acting on their behalf discloses confidential information to third party or to the public, rackAID may release additional client information or correpondence to clarify, rebut or otherwise address the disclosure. In particular, rackAID reserves the right to use client communications to rebut, clarify or otherwise describe service related issues that the client has publicly disclosed to other parties.  
**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days or by sending a notification email asking our users to accept the new privacy policy.

 **Questions**

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to privacy (at) rackaid.com.  
Phone 877-435-2444 (US and Canada)  
Phone 203-672-6639 (International Calls) Fax 203-401-8083  
Email privacy (at) rackaid.com  
Postal Address:

221 N. Hogan Street, Suite 309,

Jacksonville, Florida 32202  
Web site URL: http://www.rackaid.com/corporate/service-policies/privacy-policy/
